Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated on 16.11.2021

Reflectly ApS ('we' or 'us' or 'our') respects the privacy of our users ('user' or 'you'). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our mobile application Monefy (the 'App') or our website [monefy.me](https://monefy.me/) (collectively, the 'Site').

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the 'Last updated' date of this Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the App after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the third-party online/mobile store from which you install the App or make payments, including any in-game virtual items, which may also collect and use data about you. We are not responsible for any of the data collected by any such third party.

This Privacy Policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our Site.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THE APP.

#### What personal information do we collect from the people who use our app?

Your email address is collected if you send a “Monefy crash report” to our [reports email](mailto:reports@monefy.me "reports@monefy.me") or send an email to our [support email](mailto:support@monefy.me "support+monefy@reflectly.app").

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you in the following ways:

* To improve our website or application in order to better serve you.
* To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
* To follow up a application bug or crash investigation.

#### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information or other Personal Information entered into our app.

#### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our Site. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Dropbox

If selected, Dropbox (API) may be used to synchronize data between your devices. Please check [https://www.dropbox.com/privacy](https://www.dropbox.com/privacy "Dropbox Privacy Policy").

#### Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by [Google’s Advertising Principles](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548 "https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548"). They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

We may use Google AdSense and Admob Advertising on our Website and in our App.  
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our Site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy.

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our Site.

Google may use the advertising ID from the device on which the ad is serving to generate interests and demographics. Interests, demographics, and other data may be used to serve better targeted ads to the user. Additionally, personalized advertising (formerly known as interest-based advertising) are served via the Google Mobile Ads SDK.

#### Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page [https://myaccount.google.com/privacy](https://myaccount.google.com/privacy?pli=1#ads " https://myaccount.google.com/privacy?pli=1#ads"). Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page [https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices](https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices "www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices") or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. You can disable Google Analytics tracking within an app by going to Menu > Settings > About Monefy > Disable Google Analytics.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a Privacy Policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous Privacy Policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. You can read more [here](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf "http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf").

**In accordance with CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our Site anonymously.

Once this Privacy Policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes n our Privacy Policy page.

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking.

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

#### Amendments to Privacy Policy

We have the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice to each User. Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted here. Where appropriate, we will notify you or seek your consent. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy.

#### Contact info

If at any time you would like to contact us with your views about our privacy practices, or with any inquiry relating to your Personal Data (its correction, removal or use), you can do so by sending a message to our [contact email](mailto:support+monefy@reflectly.app "support+monefy@reflectly.app").

|

|

©2021 Reflectly ApS
